<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[Infinite Thoughts]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Infinite Thoughts]]></description>
        <link>https://thegrid.ai/deliri/</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Wed, 31 Aug 2016 12:36:24 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="https://thegrid.ai/deliri/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<p>Hi there, thanks for visiting. My name is Ase (pronounced as Ace) Deliri and I'm a GoLang developer residing in Toronto Canada. I'm a long time Apple fan, part time tech commentator. I don't advertise my blog posts to people. The reason is simple, I write these posts to improve my own learning. If you happen to stumble across and read my work, it's like you've found my study notes from school. Everything I do here is to re-enforce what I've learned. I spend my time either coding or reading books. I'm a huge fan of poetry and literature as you can see from the links. I like collecting informative, thought provoking, and highly entertaining content to share with you, my visitors. I curate them here for you to enjoy and share. In my writing, I embed lots of links to original content. There is a reason for this. Information has the greatest impact if you share it and help spread that work. When you share what you find here, you are not just helping me, you are helping all the people who created the works from which both you and I have benefited. Please remember, the web was created so we can all share knowledge. Thank you for your time. You can reach me through Twitter if you have a burning question. WHAT I SUPPORT 1. Non Aggression Principle:: Anytime a person is forced to do something against their wishes, we all lose. I don't care if someone is racist, homophobic, sexist, or violent. For society to evolve these ideas have to be proven wrong to these people, and only when they recognize it and choose the positive alternatives, can we declare victory. Forcing them by involving authorities, or public shaming fails because they will just do what is necessary to avoid the humiliation or fines. Deep down, they really haven't learned anything, or changed their mind. The forced victory is a hollow and pointless one. If you can't convince someone to arrive at an understanding on their own, keep trying. Don't resort to passive or open aggression. 2. Absolute Free Speech :: Christopher Hitchens said it best, "A short refresh of course in the classic texts on this matter, which are: John Milton's "Areopagitica", Areopagitica being the great hill of Athens, for discussion and free expression; Thomas Paine's introduction to "the Age of Reason"; and I would say John Stewart Mill's essay On Liberty, in which it is variously said.... It's not just the right of the person who speaks to be heard, it is the right of everyone in the audience to listen and to hear, and every time you silence somebody you make yourself a prisoner of your own action because you deny yourself the right to hear something. In other words your own right to hear and be exposed is as much involved in all these cases as is the right of the other to voice his or her view. Indeed as John Stewart Mill said, if all of society were agreed on the truth and beauty and value of one proposition, all except one person it would be most important in fact it would become even more important that that one heretic be heard because we would still benefit from his perhaps outrageous or appalling view." 3. Challenging ideas :: When you see an idea that is obviously false, call it out. Don't attack the person, engaging in ad-hominem is self defeating. Engage using humour, logic, and reason. Just remember we are all ignorant of one thing or another. Science uplifts you from the depths of your own ignorance and drops you off at the height of your intelligence. Sooner or later false ideas will be exposed, and eventually forgotten. Keep in mind, the amount of energy required to maintain a facade grows exponentially relative to size (how big of a lie) and scale (# of people). Truth requires nothing, is self sustaining and has no opposite. Have more questions than answers, and be excellent to each other.</p>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/deliri/53c0bd0e-0643-458f-bbcc-188394c9bb0c/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">53c0bd0e-0643-458f-bbcc-188394c9bb0c</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Aug 2016 12:35:36 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>